hi
as you can see we finally have pollution
we are using all that pollution to synthesize steel inside these godsend furnaces
by the way
unlike some of you might be thinking
this pollution is not made by the furnaces
but by all the farts of the cows around this area
insert your moma joke here
now let me do a fast recap of how far we are from building our Stargate
that we will use to go back into our basement
here you can check our different armors
one for cow ranching
and one for Faraday caging ourselves from God's thunders
by the way we now got a lot of stuff stocked up
here we have two coke ovens
these make our precious creosote oil
and some charcoal as byproduct
for the moment the oil is moved into this tank here
later we will be using it for lubricant
here we have our backup burner running on sulfur
we power it up when our steam tank runs low
and this is the workshop we build using our magic knife wand
here we have our solar boilers that give us a little bit of free steam
and the water tanks
we are also farming some slime for the raw rubber
and some normal resin
because some recipes need that
now let me show you some of my ordinary normal day life
we start by collecting some of the process's materials from our machinery
and we feed some of it back into other machinery for further processing
now using the same water cauldron
we shall make some fresh dough
and also wash some rocks
then we make some concrete
and proceed into making more furnace bricks
and also some more controllers
and now we had two more furnaces
for even more fart absorption
I'm starting to wonder
if it is time to kill some of these cows
here you can pause if you want to check what my tools are made out of
now, some of you might think that the best way of making charcoal
is by grinding a dozen of coke ovens
then proceed into making all the required setup
and then go AFK
I do not agree with that
I think it is way faster to just use a charcoal pit igniter
look at how fast you can make 9 stacks of charcoal that way
I know that automation is the core of the pack
but look
by the time you'll finish your setup
you could already have unlocked oil
which will make the oven setup look like a joke
the longest part is filling it up with logs
that is why we are going to rush the builder's wand to fix that issue as soon as we get into LV
we are compressing the charcoal into blocks
so that furnaces will run longer with no need to check on them
also gathering wood with this axe is way faster than setting up a farm in the current tier
it is now time to do some crafting
we already have resistors
so we now shall do some vacuum tubes
and now we can complete it all into our
first single electronic circuit
and that's how we got into LV
hello bot scraping the net
as you can see we now have some LV machinery
and over there we are building a new basement
we will use it for stuff that shall not be seen by normal people
we have also made a lot of improvements on the roof
we now have eight water tanks and 21 high pressure solar boilers
which will produce the equivalent of 180 EU per tick
now I think it is time for some crafting montage sequence with some low cost music
okay
that is what we have managed to get during the break
now I think the first thing we will want to craft is an EBF
we shall collect the relative materials and find a suitable spot
it will require a lot of power
so it shall be close to the tank hatch
that way we can be cheaper on the the large pipes
and now all it's left is to turn it on
and make our first aluminu ingot
however aluminium is not our only priority here
we will also need to do our shady stuff in our shady basement
we are going to turn black gold into piss colored and mold colored gold
first of all we have to extract the black stuff from the blue stuff
some stone and a pump should be able to help us with that
before starting the conversion
we will need to start stocking up some oxygen and some hydrogen
we are going to do that by electrolyzing water
we shall do that in this corner
then we connect the pipes
and we check that the gases are reaching the tanks
now we start to distill the oil
okay this is harder to explain than I thought
so let me just have a 30x speed sequence
okay so here we have
the yellow stuff, the orange stuff, the gray stuff
and the black dust
now this spaghetti bowl is too convoluted for naked human eyes
we shall cover it all with some concrete
and call it God's magic plant
now here we can dump in here the oil
and here we have the outputs
all clean with no view to the spaghetti
you might be wondering why I'm making polyethylene right now
I shall give you a hint with our next plant
as you probably have guessed we now have silicon
solar grade silicon
and now with the power of these 4 diodes
I can say
full bridge rectifier
hello human beings
we have made some progress since last time
we are now in the HV tier
let's have a fast tour of our current base
we won't be staying there for long
since we will be moving to the garden world as soon as we have access to AE2
here we have our main workshop with the machines that we are manually using every day
we have two EBFs
this is the LV array
here we have our old trusty Steam Machines
this is the MV set
and here we have our primitive vacuum freezer
let's have a look at the power generation
this is the main battery buffer
we have a cover on it
that will enable charging from diesel when the batteries run low
the detector cover activates a controller cover on a cable with a shutter module
and here we have our six combustion generators running on diesel
now let's have a look at the roof
we have our free energy production
composed of 70 high pressure solar boilers
they will produce 25 thousand steam each second
which should be around 630 EU per tick
before going into the main EU buffer
the boilers will fill this tank here
which buffers steam for the old machines
we have 3 MV turbines and 4 LV for the conversion
and here you can see the 20 water tanks filling the boilers
now let's have a look at our farm
under my feet you can see wheat, glowstone and cotton
in this contraption
we have the oreberrys for Aluminum, Gold and experience
for some reason they are not being collected
now that's an issue
it turns out that we are out of power
since it is now raining and this farm is solar powered
and here you can check the piping
first we fill the drawers
and then we process the berries into dusts
here we still have our smeltry
and here we are making some room for magic stuff
under these stairs
we are starting to making a small ore processing plant
currently we can crush, wash, centrifuge, Thermal centrifuge and sift ores
we have stocked up some silicon
here we now have diesel and TNT instead of light fuel
and this is the tank for oil and a draw for oil sands
now we shall have a crafting montage before the bonus trolling clip
okay safety goes third after fun and money
that is why we are putting on our tinfoil helmet
as you can see
weird stuff is starting to happen
now that the tin foil helmet is isolating us from God
and the instructions are too long for this video
okay now it is time to go outside
and make an oatmeal in our new microwave oven
we have a 128 volts outlet for the outside appliances
however this microwave is only 32 volts
we shall use some cable to create enough loss
to make it so that the oven can safely run on 128 volts
this should be enough
now let's cover the oven from the rain before it too late
since there is a legend about not putting eggs inside microwaves
let's make this safer by having it fed in by a pipe
and let's make us a shelter
now let's grab an egg
and here it goes
looks like the legend was true
put an egg in your microwave if you want to mow your grass effortlessly
bye bye people
it also looks like this gave us some nice effects
look at how cool a sunset looks now
now let's have some sleep in this purified area with fresh air
quick update
this is the new compressor
this is the pollution containment room
it's quite small but as you can see
it has hundreds of thousands of pollutions inside
ebfs with better coils
ice cream machine
and some other goodies
we have also built something in the nether
a wither skull farm
we then proceed to kill 9 withers
that costed us 4 backups, by the way
and that's how we wasted a lot of resources
no sword of the cosmos unfortunately
we have also done some magic research
and after a lot of work
we have finally completed the device that will bring us to god
this time we did read the instruction
and after learning from our past
this time we are doing a backup before doing an oopsie
and now we can finally go conquer the space
as you can see
the earth is flat unlike some weird books tell you
after a dangerous landing
and a long exploration
we have finally managed to find a moon dungeon
and after killing its boss
we have unlocked the tier 2 rocket schematic
and our reward is a personal dimension
where there are no dangers outside of ourselves
so, let's start paving the roads
and the layout of our new definitive base
this took quite a lot of time and effort
but nothing really worth showing
大家好
如你所见，我们终于有污染了
我们正在利用这些污染，在这些天赐的高炉中合成钢
顺便一提
与你们某些人可能想的不同
这些污染并非由高炉产生
而是来自这附近所有牛的屁
（此处可插入你妈妈的玩笑）
现在，让我快速回顾一下我们距离建造星门还有多远
而我们要用那星门重新回到我们的地下室
这里你可以看到我们的不同护甲
一套用于养牛
一套用作法拉第笼来屏蔽天雷
顺便说一句，我们现在囤积了很多东西
这里有两台焦炉
它们生产珍贵的杂酚油
以及一些木炭作为副产品
目前，油被输送到这个储罐里
稍后我们将用它来做润滑剂
这里是我们烧硫磺的备用燃烧机
当蒸汽储罐存量低时我们就启动它
这是我们用魔法小刀魔杖建造的工作室
这里我们有太阳能锅炉，提供一点点免费蒸汽
还有储水罐
我们也在种植史莱姆树以获取生橡胶
这还有一些普通树脂
因为有些配方需要它
现在让我向你展示我的日常生活
我们从收集机器处理好的材料开始
并将其中一部分喂入其他机器进行进一步加工
现在使用同一个坩埚
我们要做些新鲜面团
还要洗些石头
然后我们做一些混凝土
接着制作更多的耐火砖
还有一些控制器
现在我们又多了两个高炉
用于吸收更多的屁
我开始在想
是不是该杀掉一些牛了
你可以暂停来看看我的工具是什么做的
现在，你们有些人可能认为制作木炭的最佳方式
是造十几个焦炉
然后完成所有必需的设置
接着挂机
我不同意这种做法
我认为使用木炭堆点火器要快得多
看看用这种方法可以多快做出9组木炭
我知道自动化是这个整合包的核心
但，你瞧
等你完成你完成产线时
你可能都已经解锁石油了
那会让自动化焦炉看起来像个笑话
最耗时的部分是用原木填满它
这就是为什么我们一进入LV阶段
就要尽快做出建筑法杖来解决这个问题
我们将木炭压缩成块
这样高炉能运行更久，无需照看
而且，在当前阶段用这把斧头收集木材比建农场快得多
现在是时候做些合成了
我们已经有了电阻
现在该做些真空管了
现在我们可以把所有东西
组合成我们的第一个电路板
就这样我们进入了LV阶段
你好啊，互联网爬虫
如你所见，我们现在有了一些LV机器
在那边，我们正在建造一个新的地下室
我们将用它来存放那些不该被普通人看到的东西
我们在屋顶上也做了很多升级
我们现在有8个储水罐和21个进阶太阳能锅炉
它们将产生相当于 180 EU/t 的能量
现在我想是时候来一段低成本音乐的合成过程蒙太奇了
好了
这就是我们在休息期间设法弄到的东西
现在我想我们要做的第一件事是造一个电高炉
我们要收集相关材料并找个合适的位置
它将需要大量电力
所以应该靠近储罐舱口
这样我们可以节省更多的大管道
现在要做的就是打开它
并制造我们的第一块铝锭
然而铝并不是我们唯一的目标
我们还将在隐秘的地下室里做些见不得光的事
我们要把黑色黄金变成尿黄色和霉菌色的黄金
首先，我们必须从蓝色的东西中提取黑色的东西
一些石头和一个泵应该能帮我们做到
在开始转化之前
我们需要开始存一些氧气和氢气
我们通过在这个角落进行电解水做到这一点
然后连接管道
并检查气体是否到达储罐
现在我们开始蒸馏石油
好吧，这比我想象的更难解释
所以让我直接来一段30倍速的镜头
好了，现在我们有了
黄色的东西、橙色的东西、灰色的东西
以及黑色粉尘
现在这复杂的管道对于肉眼来说太复杂了
我们应该用混凝土把它全盖起来
并称之为上帝的魔法工厂
现在我们可以在这里输入石油
这里是输出端
全部整洁，看不到管道
你可能想知道为什么我现在要制造聚乙烯
我会用我们下一个工厂给你提示
你可能已经猜到了，我们现在有硅了
太阳能级硅
现在，借助这4个二极管的力量
我可以说
全桥整流器
大家好，人类同胞们
自上次以来，我们取得了一些进展
我们现在进入了HV阶段
让我们快速参观一下我们当前的基地
我们不会在这里待太久
因为一旦我们有了AE2，我们就会搬到私人维度去
这里是我们每天手动使用机器的主要工作室
我们有两台电高炉
这是LV机器阵列
这里是我们老旧的、可靠的蒸汽机器
这是MV机器
这里是我们原始的真空冷冻机
让我们看看发电
这是主要的电池缓冲
我们给它装了个覆盖板
当电池电量低时，它会启动柴油充电
探测覆盖板会激活电缆上的带百叶窗模块的控制器覆盖板
这里我们有六台以柴油为燃料的燃气发电机
现在让我们看看屋顶
我们有免费能源生产
由70个进阶太阳能锅炉组成
它们每秒将产生2.5万升蒸汽
大约相当于 630 EU/t
在进入主要能量缓存之前
锅炉将填满这个储罐
它为旧机器缓冲蒸汽
我们有3台MV涡轮机和4台LV涡轮机用于转换
这里你可以看到20个储水罐在为锅炉供水
现在让我们看看农场
在我脚下你可以看到小麦、荧石和棉花
在这个装置里
我们有用于铝、金和经验的矿莓
出于某种原因，它们没有被收集
这是个问题
原来是我们没电了
因为现在在下雨，而这个农场是太阳能供电的
这里你可以看到管道布置
我们先填满抽屉
然后将浆果加工成粉尘
这里我们还有冶炼厂
这里我们正在为魔法的东西腾出空间
在这些楼梯下面
我们正在开始建造一个小型矿石处理厂
目前我们可以粉碎、洗涤、离心、热离心和筛矿
我们囤积了一些硅
这里我们现在有柴油和TNT，而不是轻质燃料
这是石油的储罐和油砂的抽屉
现在，在额外的恶搞片段之前，来一段合成蒙太奇
好了，安全第三，好玩和金钱第一
这就是为什么我们要戴上锡箔头盔
如你所见
奇怪的事情要发生了
锡箔头盔将我们与上帝隔离
而说明对于这个视频来说太长了
好了，现在是时候出去了
在我们的新微波炉里做个燕麦粥
我们有一个128伏的户外电器插座
然而这微波炉只能接收32V
我们应该用一些电缆来制造足够的损耗
使得烤箱可以安全地在128伏电压下运行
这应该足够了
现在趁还来得及，把烤箱盖起来挡雨
因为有个传说说不能把鸡蛋放进微波炉
让我们用管道来输送鸡蛋来让它更安全
并给我们自己造个庇护所
现在拿个鸡蛋
放进去了
看起来传说是真的
如果你想轻松割草，就在微波炉里放个鸡蛋吧
再见各位
看起来这还给了我们一些不错的效果
看看现在的日落多酷啊
现在让我们在这个空气清新的纯净区域睡一觉
速报
这是新的压缩机
这是污染收容室
它相当小，但如你所见
里面容纳了数十万单位的污染
电力高炉配上了更好的线圈
冰箱
以及其他一些好东西
我们还在下界建了点东西
一个凋灵骷髅农场
然后我们着手杀了9只凋灵
顺便说一句，这让我们损失了4个存档备份
这就是我们如何浪费了大量资源
可惜没有寰宇之剑
我们还做了一些魔法研究
经过大量工作后
我们终于完成了将我们带往神之领域的装置
这次我们读了说明书
并从过去吸取了教训
这次我们在搞砸之前做了备份
现在我们可以最终去征服太空了
如你所见
地球是平的，不像一些奇怪的书告诉你的那样
在危险地着陆后
以及漫长的探索后
我们终于找到了月球地下城
在击败了它的Boss之后
我们解锁了二级火箭图纸
我们的奖励是一个私人维度
在那里，除了我们自己之外没有危险
那么，让我们开始铺路
并规划我们新的最终基地布局
这花费了相当多的时间和精力
但没什么真正值得展示的
（石油）
（海水）
（应该是油管主 ElectroBOOM 的梗）